Guide to the Stanford University, Electronics Laboratories, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Ireland, undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Israel, 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Request for A Study of Classical Apllications of Power Transistors, 1969 Apr 29 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Request for Realization of Microwave Pulse-Compression Filters by Means of Folded-Tape Meander Lines, 1969 Jan 2 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Request for A Redundancy Technique for Improving the Reliability of Digital Systems, 1969 Jan 12 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Italy, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Japan, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Netherlands, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Report to a Foreign National or Country, Release of, 1968 May 14 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - New Zealand, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Norway, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Poland, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Request for "Some Logarithmic Video Amplifier Analysis and Design Techniques", 1969 Mar 17 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Romania, 1958-1969 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Scotland, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Sweden, 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Switzerland, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Syria, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - U.S.S.R., 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - A, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - B, 1963-1969 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - C, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - D, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - E, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - F, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - G, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - H, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - I, 1962-1968 (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - J, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - K, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - L, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - M, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - M.I.T., 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - N, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - Casper W. Barnes, 1953 Sep 23 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Karl Spougeuberg, 1946 Aug 20 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - John Shawn Rosenbeer; HT-2, 1954 Nov 30 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Jack Snyder; HT-1, 1954 Jun 17 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Jack Snyder; U-324, 1956 Aug 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Jack Snyder; U-275, 1956 May 22 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - John Fitch; HT-3, 1955 Apr 5 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Lisa Winslow; CT-2, 1967 Dec 30 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - John Shaul; GD-1, 1954 Nov 30 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - John Snyder; V-184 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Paul A. Gary; 943, 1965 Apr 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Heinz Ruegg; Nonr 225 (31), 1965 Mar 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Heinz Ruegg; Nonr 225 (31), 1965 Apr 30 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Pierre Eliaers; AF 33(657)-11144, 1965 Jul 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - C.S. Yen; ONR (24), 1960 Aug 11 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - William Pierce; Nonr 225 (24J), 1960 Aug 25 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - C. Patel; ONR 225 (24), 1960 Sep 14 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Bob Fies; AF 2193, 1960 Sep 27 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Fred Behr; AF-6207, 1960 Sep 30 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Edward Abraham; NSF-6P-936, 1964 Oct 28 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Alex Cannara; AT(04-3)326, 1964 Nov 17 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Yen-Sun Chen; NSG-555, 1964 Nov 24 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Barry Schechtman; Nonr 225 (24), 1964 Nov 24 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Harold Weiss; NSF-GP-936, 1964 Dec 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Conrad Littig; AT(04-3)326 PA #1, 1964 Dec 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - R.P. Lagerstrom; AMC-94, 1964 Dec 8 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - M. Nagata; Nonr 225 (24), 1965 Jan 20 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Megba Shyam; SD-87-003, 1965 Feb 11 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Guido Francois; AFOSR-286, 1963 Apr 24 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Neal Kindig; SD-87-4850-47, 1963 Apr 26 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - B. Greenfield; n/a, 1963 May 7 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - R. Mehta; n/a, 1963 May 21 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - A.E.Siegman; SC 90839, 1963 Jun 14 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Waltu Krolikowski; SD-87-4850-47, 1963 Jul 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - T. Krishnan and A.R. Thompson; AF62-342, 1963 Jul 22 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Heinz Ruegg; ONR 225(31), 1964 Oct 13 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - John McMains; D936-039 AMC-03761(E), 1964 Oct 15 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Richard Koyama; SD-87, 1964 Oct 20 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-259 Soohoo, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-262 Siegman, 1954-1957 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-273 Gillmore, 1954-1957 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-274 Pratt, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-276 Soohoo, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-279 Reid, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-280 Goldfarb, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-281 Barsacq, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-282 Goldfarb, 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-284 Falconer, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-286 Lin, 1956 Jun 20 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-287 Ishikawa, 1956 Jun 20 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-285 Pittit, 1956 Jun 20 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-288 De Grasse, 1956 Jun 21 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-290 Yhap, 1956 Jun 26 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-289 Morris, 1956 Jun 22 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-291 Ligomenides, 1956 Jun 26 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-292 Spilker, 1956 Jun 26 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-303 Jones, 1957 Nov 25 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-318 Meneses, 1956 Jul 24 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-415 Chang, 1957 Jul 11 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-417 Seigmen, 1959 Aug 18 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-423 Terman, 1957 Oct 2 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory U-427 Kurzweli, 1957 Oct 3 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Nasa-ASEE Summer Institute Stanford Ames Research Program Final Report, 1976 Oct 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Nasa-ASEE Summer Institute Stanford Ames Research Program Final Report, 1974 Sep 20 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Nasa-ASEE Summer Institute Stanford Ames Research Program Final Report, 1972 Sep 25 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - A Theory of Interpretive Architectures: Some Notes on Del Design and a Fortran Case Study Technical Report No. 171, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - A Theory of Interpretive Architectures: Ideal Language Machines Technical Report No. 170, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Energy Models and Large-Scale Systems Optimization Technical Report SOL 76-26, 1976 Nov (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - System Considerations in the Design of Residue Processors Annual Technical Report No. L722-2, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Acoustic Reflection Microscope G.L. Report No. 2894, 1978 Dec (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - The National Environmental Policy Act. and Federal Water Resources Planning: Effects and Effectiveness, 1977 Dec (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Decomposition in Fixed Point Computation Technical Report Sol 77-32, 1977 Dec (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Superconducting Power Transmission Lines Final Progress Report for the National Science Foundation G.L. Report No. 2641, 1976 Dec (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Laser Induced Energy Transfer G.L. Report No. 2920, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - A Selective Analytical Bibliography for Social Impact Assessment Report IPM 1, 1977 Nov (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - An Algorithm for a Piecewise Linear Model of Trade and Production with Negative Prices and Bankruptcy Technical Report Sol 76-19, 1976 Aug (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Formation and Propagation of Vortex Rings in Axisymmetic, Bounded, Pulsed Flow, 1976 Dec (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Turnable Lasers and Coherent Light Techniques for High Resolution Ultraviolet Spectroscopy Technical Report No. 6. G.L. Report No 2758; N00014-75-C-0841, 1977 Dec (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Laboratory Activity Report SSRL Report 78/10, 1978 Nov (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - The Computation of Economic Equilbria by Path Methods Technical report SOL 77-26, 1977 Oct (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Determining Prices and Monetary Flows of the Pilot Energy Model Technical Report SOL 76-28, 1976 Oct (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Modeling Personal Computation of Goods in the Pilot Energy Model Technical Report SOL 76-17, 1976 Aug (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Convergence Properties of a Pies-Type Algorithm for Non-Integrable Functions Technical Report SOL 77-33, 1977 Dec (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Infrastructure Dynamics: A Selected Bibliography IPM Report No. 5, 1978 Jan (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Fundamentals of a Continuous Time Simplex Method Technical Report SOL 78-26, 1978 Dec (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Final Report on A Feasibility Study on the Growth of Bulk GaN Single Crystals; N00019-78-C-0105, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Pricing Underemployed Capacity in a Linear Economic Model Technical Report SOL 79-2, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Market Structure in a Computer Network Report No. 17, 1979 Feb (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Parallel Incoherent Optical Matrix-Vector Multiplier Technical Report No. L-723-1, 2/15/1979 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Siple VLF Transmitter Data 1978: Selected Records from Roberval, Canada and ISEE-1 Technical Report No. VLF79-1, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - S-1 Architecture Manual Technical Report No. 161, 1979 Jan (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Laser-Induced Interactions by W.R. Green G.L. Report No. 2936; N00014-78-C-0403, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - An Introduction to the DDL-P Language Technical Report No. 163, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - A Statistical Study of Service Interruptions at the SLAC Triplex Multiprocessor Technical Report No. 141, 1978 May (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - DDL-P Command Language Manual Technical Report No. 164, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - High Performance Preprocessor Electronics for Ultrasound Imaging Technical report No. G557-3, 1979 May (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - T.E.C.A.P. An Automated Characterization System Technical report No. 5017-1, 1979 March (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Projected Lagrangian Methods Based on the Trajectories of Penalty and Barrier Functions Technical Report SOL 78-23, 1978 Nov (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - On the Solution of Large, Structured Linear Complementary Problems: I Technical Report 73-4, 1973 April (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Second Order Characteristics of Pseudoconvex Functions Technical Report 73-12, 1976 June (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - A Homotopy Based Approach to Unconstrained Optimization Technical Report 76-14, 1976 July (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Algorithmic Equivalence in Quadratic Programming I: A Least-Distance Programming Problem Technical Report 76-26, 1976 Oct (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Quick Optimal Weekly Scheduling with Two Consecutive Days Off Technical report 77-1, 1977 Jan (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - A Probabilistic Model for Diagnosis in Digital Systems Technical Report No. 144, 1978 Sept (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Reliable Synchronizations and Matching in Redundant Systems Technical Report No. 169, 1979 Jan (Box 39, Folder 43)